// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following has a global scope in the program?",
    answer: " Marcos",
    options: [
      " Formal parameters",
      " Constants",
      " Marcos",
      " Local Variables"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following statements about functions is false?",
    answer: " The maximum number of arguments a function can take is 128",
    options: [
      "The main() function can be called recursively",
      "Functions cannot return more than one value at a time",
      "A function can have multiple return statements with different return values",
      " The maximum number of arguments a function can take is 128"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "malloc() function used in dynamic allocation is available in which header file?",
    answer: "stdlib.h",
    options: [
      "stdio.h",
      "stdlib.h",
      "conio.h",
      "mem.h"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the range of double data type for a 16-bit compiler?",
    answer: "-1.7e-308 to +1.7e-308",
    options: [
      "-1.7e-328 to +1.7e-328",
      "-1.7e-348 to +1.7e-348",
      "-1.7e-308 to +1.7e-308",
      "-1.7e-328 to +1.7e-328"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The function scanf is used to ___",
    answer: "Input a set of values",
    options: [
      "To take logical decisions",
      "Input a set of values",
      "Print a set of values",
      "Do mathematical manipulations"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Each element of a structure can be _____",
    answer: " Read and printed as a separate data item ",
    options: [
      " Read and printed as a separate data item ",
      " Printed as a separate data item ",
      " Read as a separate data item ",
      " None of these "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In the for loop structure, which statement is present?",
    answer: " Both (a) & (b) ",
    options: [
      " Assign Statement ",
      " Alter Statement",
      " Both (a) & (b) ",
      " None of these "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following declarations is not correct?",
    answer: " unsigned float d; ",
    options: [
      " unsigned float d; ",
      " unsigned char c; ",
      " int b = 4; ",
      " float a; "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following input function cannot be used to input multiword string in a single function call? ",
    answer: " getch() ",
    options: [
      " getch() ",
      " gets() ",
      " scanf() ",
      " None of the above "
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If the function returns no value then it is called ____",
    answer: " Void function ",
    options: [
      " Data type function ",
      " Calling function ",
      " Main function ",
      " Void function "
    ]
  },
];